There's a deep sickness that's in this country right now.
And it pains me a lot to acknowledge it.
Yeah, the amazing thing is you look at Portland
and you see fires all over the place.
You see fights and I mean, just violence.
It's just so crazy.
And then you talk to the governor
and she's acts like everything is totally normal.
There's nothing wrong.
It's almost like, are you waking up from a dream or something?
You see it on your network.
You see it all over the place.
And it's so bad, it's so crazy.
It's like the movies you see for the kids.
I guess not only the kids, adults also
where you have these bombed out cities
and these bombed out people.
It's like worse than that.
I don't think they could make a movie as bad.
And then the governor will get up and say,
I don't know why they're coming here.
It's such a wonderful place.
And the amazing thing is the people want us to be there.
The people, when they get the real people that live there,
many of them have left,
but the real people want us to be the same thing in Chicago.
So they've had 60, 70 murders over a short period of time.
Murders, people that got shot.
They've had hundreds of people shot.
And then a guy like Pritzker or this low IQ mayor gets up.
I mean, he got up, he's got a 5% approval rating
and the people are all against him.
They want people to come.
Beautiful black women are wearing a MAGA hat
last night on television.
Beautiful people.
And they said, we don't care who comes, just stop the crime.
They don't care, frankly, they don't care
if it's National Guard, military,
send in anybody you want, stop the crime.
And they're afraid to go out.
They can't even go out.
And then a guy like Pritzker, think of that.
50, 60, 70 people over a short period of time murdered,
actually murdered, mostly gun violence,
but knives, but gun violence, they're murdered.
And hundreds of people shot.
They had one weekend where they had like 18 murdered
and 71 shot.